J: Sarah! Sorry I’m late!
S: Same old Jake.
You always were late for everything.
Good to see you.
You look well.
J: You look fantastic.
S: Thank you.
What would you like? I’m having a flat white.
J: Oh, er…The same for me.
And a croissant or something…
It’s really great to see you, Sarah, just like old times.
You haven’t changed.
And…I miss you…
We need to meet again before I go back to the States.
Are you doing anything on Saturday?
S: Well, actually I’m…
J: Lunch? Dinner? Breakfast?
S: Jake, there’s something I need to tell you.
I’m not single now, in fact, um… in fact I’m seeing someone, he’s called Mike,
and… we’re getting married this Saturday.
That’s why I’m so busy all this week…
J: Wow! Um, that’s… That’s great news!
I wish you all the best!
S: Thanks, Jake.
A: Jake, it’s you! How’s the conference? You didn’t pick up my messages… Oh! Is this…?